Guide to the Philip Ross Collection of NLRB Documents 1927-1974
Ross, Philip Collection of NLRB Documents
- 13-CA-5401; Jones Transfer Company, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 9)
- 13-CA-5403; Berry Electric Contracting Company, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 10)
- 13-CA-5404; Jos. T. Ryerson & Son, Inc., 1963 (Box 143, Folder 11)
- 13-CA-5405; Automatic Bending Co., 1963 (Box 143, Folder 12)
- 13-CA-5407; Pure Milk Association, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 13)
- 13-CA-5408; Elgin Daily Courier News, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 14)
  Elgin, Illinois
- 13-CA-5410; Gateway Chemical and Pontonier, Inc., 1963 (Box 143, Folder 15)
- 13-CA-5411; Quaker Industries, Inc., 1963 (Box 143, Folder 16)
  Antioch, Illinois
- 13-CA-5414; Illinois Bell Telephone Company, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 17)
- 13-CA-5415; Chicago Federation of Musicians, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 18)
- 13-CA-5416; Armored Express Corp., 1963 (Box 143, Folder 19)
- 13-CA-5419; Johnson Motors, Division of Outboard Marine Corporation, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 20)
  Waukegan, Illinois
- 13-CA-5420; General Binding Corporation, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 21)
  Northbrook, Illinois
- 13-CA-5421; Irvan Laskey-Ideal Service Station, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 22)
- 13-CA-5422; Hotpoint, A Division of General Electric, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 23)
- 13-CA-5422; Hotpoint, A Division of General Electric Co., 1963 (Box 143, Folder 24)
- 13-CA-5422; Hotpoint, A Division of General Electric Co., 1963 (Box 143, Folder 25)
- 13-CA-5423; Ward's Baking Company, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 26)
- 13-CA-5425; Calumet Area Joint Grievance Committee Cartage & Freight Industry, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 27)
- 13-CA-5428; Corn Products Refining Co., 1963 (Box 143, Folder 28)
  Argo, Illinois
- 13-CA-5430; Fred A Niles Communications Centers, Inc., 1963 (Box 143, Folder 29)
- 13-CA-5431; Aluminum Distributors, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 30)
  Forest Park, Illinois
- 13-CA-5432; Universal Hat and Cap Co., 1963 (Box 143, Folder 31)
- 13-CA-5434; Lanzit Corrugated Box Company, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 32)
- 13-CA-5437; Charles Lenz & Sons, Inc., 1963 (Box 143, Folder 33)
- 13-CA-5438; Irving Spector, Barry Shuman and Jerome Maltz, d/b/a The Imperial Inn, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 34)
- 13-CA-5443; Mississippi Valley Barge Line Company, 1963 (Box 144, Folder 1)
- 13-CA-5445; Standard Stamping & Perforating Co., 1963 (Box 144, Folder 2)
- 13-CA-5442; Glass Shower Door, 1963 (Box 144, Folder 3)
- 13-CA-3441; Mid-West Coil & Transformer, Co., 1963 (Box 144, Folder 4)
- 13-CA-5464; Rumson Terminals, Inc., 1963 (Box 144, Folder 6)
- 13-CA-5448; Acme Industrial Company, 1963 (Box 144, Folder 7)
- 13-CA-5463; M C Clendon Corporation, 1963 (Box 144, Folder 8)
- 13-CA-5447; Dormeyer Industries, 1963 (Box 144, Folder 9)
- 13-CA-5447; Dormeyer Industries, 1963 (Box 144, Folder 10)
- 10-CC-440; Local 136, Electrical Workers, 1963 (Box 144, Folder 11)
- 13-CA-5452; Spiegel, Inc., 1963 (Box 145, Folder 1)
- 13-CA-5453; Western Transportation, 1963 (Box 145, Folder 2)
- 13-CA-5454; Ditto, Inc., 1963 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  Lincolnwood, Illinois
- 13-CA-5456; Cinaudagraph, Inc., 1963 (Box 145, Folder 4)
- 13-CA-5457; Takin Bros. Freight Line, Inc., 1963 (Box 145, Folder 5)
- 13-CA-5459; Republic Steel Company, 1963 (Box 145, Folder 6)
- 13-CA-5459; Republic Steel Corporation, 1963 (Box 145, Folder 7)
- 13-CA-5460; Bradley and Vrooman Company, 1963 (Box 145, Folder 8)
- 13-CA-5461; Chain Velt Company, 1963 (Box 145, Folder 9)
- 13-CA-5462; Bell Electric Company, 1963 (Box 145, Folder 10)
- 13-CA-5463; The McLendon Corporation, 1963 (Box 145, Folder 11)
- 13-CA-5466; Elgin Import Motors, Inc., 1963 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  Dundee, Illinois
- 13-CA-5466; Elgin Import Motors, Inc., 1963 (Box 146, Folder 2)
- 13-CA-5471; National Video Corporation, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 3)
- 13-CA-5472; Hart Schaffner & Marx, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 4)
- 13-CA-5473; Metal Coating Corporation, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 5)
- 13-CA-5476; Ford Motor Company, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 6)
- 13-CA-5479; United Food Management Services, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  South Chicago, Illinois
- 13-CA-5485; The Rust Engineering Company, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 8)
- 13-CA-5487; Riverdale Plating & Heat Treating Co., 1963 (Box 146, Folder 9)
- 13-CA-5487; Riverdale Plating & Heat Treating Co., 1963 (Box 146, Folder 10)
- 13-CA-5487; Riverdale Plating & Heat Treating Co., 1963 (Box 146, Folder 11)
- 13-CA-5487; Riverdale Plating & Heat, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 12)
- 13-CA-5488; Elwood Industries, Inc., 1963 (Box 146, Folder 13)
- 13-CA-5492; Burgess-Norton Co., 1963 (Box 146, Folder 14)
  Geneva, Illinois
- 13-CA-5492; Burgess-Norton Co., 1963 (Box 146, Folder 15)
- 13-CA-5494; C E B Printing Ink Co., 1963 (Box 146, Folder 16)
- 13-CA-5495; Delta Star Electric Co., Division of H. K. Porter, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 17)
- 13-CA-5496; Consolidated Freightways of Delaware, Inc., 1963 (Box 146, Folder 18)
- 13-CA-5498; American Optical Company, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 19)
- 13-CA-5500; Victor Mfg. & Gasket Co., 1963 (Box 146, Folder 20)
- 13-CA-5502; D & L Transport, Inc., 1963 (Box 146, Folder 21)
- 13-CA-5504; Apar Mfg., Inc., 1963 (Box 146, Folder 22)
  Bridgeview, Illinois
- 13-CA-5505; Polo Products Company, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 23)
- 13-CA-5505; Polo Products Company, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 24)
- 13-CA-5506; R. Lavin & Sons, Inc., 1963 (Box 146, Folder 25)
- 13-CA-5507; Jewel Tea Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 146, Folder 26)
- 13-CA-5303; General Binding Corporation, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 1)
- 13-CA-5304; Brunner Enterprises, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 2)
- 13-CA-5305; Letter Fabricators, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 3)
- 13-CA-5309; Elco Electronics, Inc., 1963 (Box 147, Folder 4)
- 13-CA-5310; Colonial Mobile Homes, Inc., 1963 (Box 147, Folder 5)
- 13-CA-5311; Churchill Cabinet Co., 1963 (Box 147, Folder 6)
- 13-CA-5315; Imco Container Co., 1963 (Box 147, Folder 7)
- 13-CA-5319; The McLendon Corporation d/b/a Radio Station Wyner, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 8)
- 13-CA-5320; Chicago Corned Beef Corporation and Papa David Sausage Manufacturing Company, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 9)
- 13-CA-5321; B. M. Reeves Corporation of Illinois, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 10)
- 13-CA-5325; Chicago Tribune Co., 1963 (Box 147, Folder 11)
- 13-CA-5326; Haynes Lithograph Co., 1963 (Box 147, Folder 12)
- 13-CA-5328; The Imperial Inn, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 13)
- 13-CA-5329; General Chauffeurs, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 14)
  Joliet, Illinois
- 13-CA-5330; Arkansas Best Freight System, Inc., 1963 (Box 147, Folder 15)
- 13-CA-5331; Terminal Transport, Inc., 1963 (Box 147, Folder 16)
- 13-CA-5332; Cinch Manufacturing Company, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 17)
- 13-CA-5333; Spartus Corporation, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 18)
- 13-CA-5334; Addis Rubber Company, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 19)
- 13-CA-5335; Book Supply Co., 1963 (Box 147, Folder 20)
- 13-CA-5336; A. F. Dormeyer Mfg. Co., 1963 (Box 147, Folder 21)
- 13-CA-5339; Chicago Block Company, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 22)
- 13-CA-5340; LaSalle Steel Company, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 23)
- 13-CA-5342; Saxon Paint Stores, Inc., 1963 (Box 147, Folder 24)
- 13-CA-5342; Saxon Paint Stores, Inc., 1963 (Box 147, Folder 25)
- 13-CA-5344; Union Carbide and Chemical Company, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 26)
- 13-CA-5345; Cadillac Glass Company, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 27)
- 13-CA-5327; G. M. Laboratories, Inc., 1963 (Box 147, Folder 28)
- 13-CA-5509; Accurate Die and Stamping Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 148, Folder 1)
- 13-CA-5510; Able Electric Polishing Co., 1963 (Box 148, Folder 2)
- 13-CA-5511; Gus Good Food Restaurant, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 3)
- 13-CA-5514; Aluminum Company of America, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 4)
- 13-CA-5516; Dole Valve Company, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 5)
- 13-CA-5516; Dole Valve Company, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 6)
- 13-CA-5518; Butler Specialty Company, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 7)
- 13-CA-5519; Cotton Specialty Co., 1963 (Box 148, Folder 8)
- 13-CA-5520; Consolidated Freightways, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 9)
- 13-CA-5521; Sinko Mfg. Co., 1963 (Box 148, Folder 10)
- 13-CA-5522; All States Service, Inc., 1963 (Box 148, Folder 11)
- 13-CA-5523; Earl Schieb, Inc., 1963 (Box 148, Folder 12)
- 13-CA-5524; Northern Illinois Gas Company, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 13)
- 13-CA-5526; Harper Leather Company, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 14)
- 13-CA-5526; Harper Leather Goods Mfg. Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 148, Folder 15)
- 13-CA-5527; White Printing Company, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 16)
- 13-CA-5528; B and L Garage Company, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 17)
- 13-CA-5529; Simmons Mattress Company, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 18)
  Munster, Indiana
- 13-CA-5530; Aurora Steel Products, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 19)
- 13-CA-5532; Le Marge Mailing Service, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 20)
- 13-CA-5533; Thrall Car Manufacturing Company, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 21)
- 13-CA-5534; American Furniture Novelty Company, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 22)
- 13-CA-5535; Grocerland Cooperatives, Inc., 1963 (Box 148, Folder 23)
- 13-CA-5539; Air Reduction Sales Company, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 24)
- 13-CA-5540; Rialto Parking Service, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 25)
- 13-CA-5541; Greyhound Bus Lines, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 26)
- 13-CA-5543; Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Company, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 1)
- 13-CA-5544; Sampson Tank & Mfg. Corp., 1963 (Box 149, Folder 2)
- 13-CA-5546; Martin Oil Service, Inc., 1963 (Box 149, Folder 3)
- 13-CA-5547; Illinois Condenser Company, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 4)
- 13-CA-5549; Ideal Auto Parts Co., 1963 (Box 149, Folder 5)
- 13-CA-5552; Continental Oil Company, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 6)
- 13-CA-5553; Sheridan Peter Pan Studios, Inc., 1963 (Box 149, Folder 7)
- 13-CA-5554; Young Spring and Wire Corporation, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 8)
- 13-CA-5554; Young Spring & Wire Corporation, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 9)
- 13-CA-5554; Young Spring & Wire Corporation, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 10)
- 13-CA-5554; Young Spring & Wire Corporation, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 11)
- 13-CA-5557; Local 719 United Auto Workers, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 12)
- 13-CA-5558; Victor Gasket Company, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 13)
- 13-CA-5560; Poole Bros., Inc., 1963 (Box 149, Folder 14)
- 13-CA-5564; Advance Finishing Company, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 15)
- 13-CA-5565; Solo Cup Company, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 16)
- 13-CA-5568; Feature Products, Inc., 1963 (Box 149, Folder 17)
- 13-CA-5570; The Goss Company, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 18)
- 13-CA-5574; Illinois Bell Telephone Co., 1963 (Box 149, Folder 19)
- 13-CA-5575; Johnson Paving Co., 1963 (Box 149, Folder 20)
- 13-CA-5576; Ideal Roller and Mfg. Co., 1963 (Box 149, Folder 21)
- 13-CA-5577; Martin Oil Service, Inc., 1963 (Box 149, Folder 22)
- 13-CA-5579; Continental Filling Corporation, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 23)
  Hobart, Indiana
- 13-CA-5580; Chriben Builders, Inc., 1963 (Box 149, Folder 24)
- 13-CA-5580; Chriburn Builders, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 25)
- 13-CA-5581; Trumbull Asphalt Company, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 26)
- 13-CA-5581; Trumbull Asphalt Company, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 27)
- 13-CA-5583; Norwalk Truck Lines, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 28)
- 13-CA-5585; Nylok Corp., 1963 (Box 149, Folder 29)
- 13-CA-5586; Outboard Marine Corporation, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 30)
- 13-CA-5587; Illinois Condenser Company, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 31)
- 13-CA-5589; Gary Steel Supply Co., 1963 (Box 149, Folder 32)
- 13-CA-5589; Gary Steel Supply Co., 1963 (Box 149, Folder 33)
- 13-CA-5590; Marsco Manufacturing Co., 1963 (Box 150, Folder 1)
- 13-CA-5591; Surface Finishers, Inc., 1963 (Box 150, Folder 2)
- 13-CA-5592; Roth Rubber Company, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 3)
- 13-CA-5597; Bell Electric Company, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 4)
- 13-CA-5601; E. J. Korvette, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  Oak Lawn, Illinois
- 13-CA-5604; Erickson Electrical Equipment Company, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 6)
- 13-CA-5605; Pathfinder Corporation, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 7)
- 13-CA-5607; Crown Metal Mfg. Company, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 8)
- 13-CA-5609; Pinkerton's national Detective Agency, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 9)
- 13-CA-5610; Englehardt Construction Company, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 10)
- 13-CA-5614; Alberto Culver, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 11)
- 13-CA-5618; Box Finishers, Inc., 1963 (Box 150, Folder 12)
- 13-CA-5619; Dealers Transit, Inc., 1963 (Box 150, Folder 13)
- 13-CA-5622; Acme Acoustics Inc., 1963 (Box 150, Folder 14)
- 13-CA-5623; Utica Communications Corp., 1963 (Box 150, Folder 15)
- 13-CA-5624; Green Briar Hotel, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 16)
- 13-CA-5625; Solo Cup Company, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 17)
- 13-CA-5627; Glass Shower Door Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 150, Folder 18)
- 13-CA-5630; Orington Hotel, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 19)
- 13-CA-5630; Orrington Hotel, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 20)
- 13-CA-5631; L. E. Alport, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 21)
- 13-CA-5632; Industrial Die Casting Co., 1963 (Box 150, Folder 22)
- 13-CA-5632; Industrial Die Casting Company, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 23)
- 13-CA-5634; Interstate Bakeries Corp., 1963 (Box 150, Folder 24)
- 13-CA-5636; Mid-City Architectural Iron Company, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 25)
- 13-CA-5639; Spector Mid States Trucking Co., 1963 (Box 150, Folder 26)
- 13-CA-5641; Johnson Motors, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 27)
- 13-CA-5641; Johnson Motors, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 28)
- 13-CA-5644; Mike Chiapetti Packing Co., 1963 (Box 150, Folder 29)
- 13-CA-5647; Clark Rug and Carpet Mart, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 30)
- 13-CA-5648; Republic Packaging Co. Bois Specialty Co., 1963 (Box 150, Folder 31)
- 13-CA-5649; Young Spring & Wire Corporation, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 32)
- 13-CA-5651; Carl Goldberg Model Co., 1963 (Box 150, Folder 33)
- 13-CA-5655; Astro Metallics Corporation, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 34)
  Harwood Heights, Illinois
- 13-CA-5656; Nickey Chevrolet Sales, Inc., 1963 (Box 150, Folder 35)
- 13-CA-5657; Cook Electric Company, 1963 (Box 150, Folder 36)
- 13-CA-5691; Ford Motor Company, 1963 (Box 151, Folder 1)
- 13-CA-5691; Ford Motor Company, 1963 (Box 151, Folder 2)
- 13-CA-5690; Miehle, Goss, and Dexter, 1963 (Box 151, Folder 3)
- 13-CA-5688; Index Sales Corporation, 1963 (Box 151, Folder 4)
- 13-CA-5686; American Bridge Div. of U. S. Steel, 1963 (Box 151, Folder 5)
- 13-CA-5684; Victory Electronics and Research Corporation, 1963 (Box 151, Folder 6)
- 13-CA-5681; Walter's Union Market, 1963 (Box 151, Folder 7)
- 13-CA-5680; Northern Indiana Tile Contractors Association, Inc., 1963 (Box 151, Folder 8)
- 13-CA-5679; Shure Brothers Company, 1963 (Box 151, Folder 9)
- 13-CA-5678; P. A. Sturtevant Company, 1963 (Box 151, Folder 10)
- 13-CA-5671; Bradley Industries Inc., 1963 (Box 151, Folder 11)
- 13-CA-5676; Advance Enameling Co., 1963 (Box 151, Folder 12)
- 13-CA-5673; Campbell 66 Express, Inc., 1963 (Box 151, Folder 13)
- 13-CA-5669; American Oil Company, 1963 (Box 151, Folder 14)
- 13-CA-5668; Chicago Car Advertising, 1963 (Box 151, Folder 15)
- 13-CA-5667; Allied Wire Products, Inc., 1963 (Box 151, Folder 16)
- 13-CA-5666; Arrow Houseware Products, Inc., 1963 (Box 151, Folder 17)
- 13-CA-5665; Hall Aluminum Company, 1963 (Box 151, Folder 18)
- 13-CA-5664; Kabo, Inc., 1963 (Box 151, Folder 19)
- 13-CA-5662; Crest Motors, Inc., 1963 (Box 151, Folder 20)
- 13-CA-5661; Outboard Marine Corporation, 1963 (Box 151, Folder 21)
- 13-CA-5660; Edmier Company, 1963 (Box 151, Folder 22)
- 13-CA-5659; Youngstown Sheet & Tube Company, 1963 (Box 151, Folder 23)
- 13-CA-5693; Jose Bethancourt, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 1)
- 13-CA-5694; Dan Belloc, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 2)
- 13-CA-5696; Field Container Corp., 1963 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  Elk Grove Village, Illinois
- 13-CA-5698; Art Lamp Co., 1963 (Box 152, Folder 4)
- 13-CA-5699; Montgomery Ward & Co., 1963 (Box 152, Folder 5)
- 13-CA-5701; Thompson Terminal Inc., 1963 (Box 152, Folder 6)
- 13-CA-5703; Electric Storage Battery Company, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 7)
- 13-CA-5704; Dravo Construction Corporation, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  Riverdale, Illinois
- 13-CA-5708; Cal Harbor Spotting Service, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 9)
- 13-CA-5709; Kitchens of Sara Lee, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 10)
- 13-CA-5713; Glass Shower Company, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 11)
- 13-CA-5714; Speed-O-Print Corp., 1963 (Box 152, Folder 12)
- 13-CA-5715; Johns-Manville, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 13)
  Rockdale, Illinois
- 13-CA-5716; Harry Davies Molding Co., 1963 (Box 152, Folder 14)
- 13-CA-5717; national Rawhide Mfg. Co., 1963 (Box 152, Folder 15)
- 13-CA-5718; Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 16)
  North Chicago, Illinois
- 13-CA-5719; Chicago Towel Company, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 17)
- 13-CA-5721; Samson Tank Mfg. Corp., 1963 (Box 152, Folder 18)
- 13-CA-5726; Skil Corporation, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 19)
- 13-CA-5727; Conrad Hilton Hotel, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 20)
- 13-CA-5730; Industrial Gear Manufacturing Co., 1963 (Box 152, Folder 21)
- 13-CA-5734; Martin Oil Service Inc., 1963 (Box 152, Folder 22)
- 13-CA-5734; Martin Oil Service, Inc., 1963 (Box 152, Folder 23)
- 13-CA-5735; Apex Paper Box Company, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 24)
- 13-CA-5737; Village Cab Company, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 25)
- 13-CA-5738; Tri-Aire Corporation, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 26)
- 13-CA-5739; Yeomen Bros., 1963 (Box 152, Folder 27)
- 13-CA-5742; General Motors Corporation, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 28)
- 13-CA-5744; Del Farm Food Stores, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 29)
- 13-CA-5751; Chicago Playboy Club, Inc., 1963 (Box 152, Folder 30)
- 13-CA-5745; Aurora Pump Division, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 31)
- 13-CA-5747; The Ruberoid Company Mastic Tile Division, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 32)
- 13-CA-5748; Kropp Forge Company, 1963 (Box 152, Folder 33)
- 13-CA-5805; Park Dearborn Hotel, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 1)
- 13-CA-5805; Park Dearborn Hotel, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  Chicago, Hotel
- 13-CA-5807; Abernathy Taxi Association, Inc., 1963 (Box 153, Folder 3)
- 13-CA-5808; John F. Cuneo Company, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 4)
- 13-CA-5814; Glendenning Motorways, Inc., 1963 (Box 153, Folder 5)
- 13-CA-5815; Chicago Car Advertising, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 6)
- 13-CA-5821; Berg Airlectro, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 7)
- 13-CA-5804; Standard Oil Company of Indiana, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 8)
- 13-CA-5801; Indak Manufacturing Company, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 9)
- 13-CA-5800; Zeller Packing Company, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 10)
- 13-CA-5788; National Metalware, Inc., 1963 (Box 153, Folder 11)
- 13-CA-5791; Jack Gray and Company, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 12)
- 13-CA-5792; Publishers Offset Corporation, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 13)
- 13-CA-5793; Princeton Plating Company, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 14)
- 13-CA-5795; Sterling Drum Company, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 15)
- 13-CA-5795; Sterling Drum Company, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 16)
- 13-CA-5798; Huber & Huber Motor Express Inc., 1963 (Box 153, Folder 17)
- 13-CA-5799; Howe Richardson Scale Company, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 18)
- 13-CA-5772; Fleischman Distilling Corporation, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 19)
  Plainfield, Illinois
- 13-CA-5774; Ridge Car Wash, Inc., 1963 (Box 153, Folder 20)
- 13-CA-5775; Hertz Corporation, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 21)
- 13-CA-5781; Takin Freight Line, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 22)
- 13-CA-5782; Radio Station WNMP - Semrow Broadcasting, Inc., 1963 (Box 153, Folder 23)
- 13-CA-5783; The Chicago Tribune, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 24)
- 13-CA-5785; Harwood Electronics Co., 1963 (Box 153, Folder 25)
- 13-CA-5787; Local 550, Air Line Stewards and Stewardesses Association, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 26)
- 13-CA-5765; Barber-Greene Company, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 27)
- 13-CA-5768; Panda Terminals, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 28)
- 13-CA-5770; Harwood Mfg. Co. and Harwood Electronics Co., 1963 (Box 153, Folder 29)
- 13-CA-5771; 6656 Liquor Corp. and Melvin Weinbaum, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 30)
- 13-CA-5760; Ball Bros. Inc., 1963 (Box 153, Folder 31)
- 13-CA-5756; B. Heller & Company, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 32)
- 13-CA-5758; Barrett, Inc., 1963 (Box 153, Folder 33)
- 13-CA-5752; Star West Cartage Co., 1963 (Box 153, Folder 34)
- 13-CA-5755; Hotpoint, A Division of General Electric Company, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 35)
- 13-CA-5822; Universal Plumbing & Heating Supply Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 154, Folder 1)
- 13-CA-5823; Budd Company, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 2)
- 13-CA-5824; Rexel Wine and Liquors, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 3)
- 13-CA-5825; Szabo Food Service, Inc., 1963 (Box 154, Folder 4)
- 13-CA-5827; Edmier, Inc., 1963 (Box 154, Folder 5)
- 13-CA-5828; Pioneer Astro Industries, Inc., 1963 (Box 154, Folder 6)
- 13-CA-5829; Aristocrat Inns of A., Inc., 1963 (Box 154, Folder 7)
- 13-CA-5830; Regal China Company, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 8)
- 13-CA-5832; Alberto Culver Company, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 9)
- 13-CA-5834; Rex Chain Belt Company, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 10)
- 13-CA-5835; Argus Incorporated, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 11)
- 13-CA-5836; Archer-Daniels-Midland Company, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 12)
- 13-CA-5837; Sunbeam Corporation, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 13)
- 13-CA-5839; St. Joe Paper Company, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 14)
  Northlake, Illinois
- 13-CA-5841; Mach Equipment Company, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 15)
- 13-CA-5842; Fred Olson Motor Service, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 16)
- 13-CA-5845; Inland Steel Company, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 17)
- 13-CA-5850; G. A. Rafel & Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 154, Folder 18)
- 13-CA-5851; Potlatch-Forest, Inc., 1963 (Box 154, Folder 19)
  Mundelein, Illinois
- 13-CA-5855; Watson-Wilson Transportation System, Inc., 1963 (Box 154, Folder 20)
- 13-CA-5856; Guarantee Generator, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 21)
- 13-CA-5857; Tuthill Pump Company, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 22)
- 13-CA-5860; Murphy Motor Express, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 23)
- 13-CA-5862; Ford Motor Company, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 24)
- 13-CA-5863; Greyhound Corporation, Central Greyhound Lines Div., 1963 (Box 154, Folder 25)
- 13-CA-5865; Kasle Steel Corporation, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 26)
- 13-CA-5867; Eastern Greyhound Lines, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 27)
- 13-CA-5869; The Sampson Company, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 28)
- 13-CA-5870; Interstate Cooperation Company, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 29)
- 13-CA-5872; Western Terminal Company, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 30)
- 13-CA-5877; Vari Products Company, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 31)
- 13-CA-5878; ITT General Controls, Inc., 1963 (Box 154, Folder 32)
- 13-CA-5885; Chesire, Inc., 1963 (Box 154, Folder 33)
- 13-CA-5886; Wilson Jones Company, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 34)
- 13-CA-5887; Jos. T. Ryerson & Son, Inc., 1963 (Box 154, Folder 35)
- 13-CA-5890; Acra Electric Corporation, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 36)
- 13-CA-5891; Burton-Dixie, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 37)
- 13-CA-5893; The Santa Fe Trail Transportation Company, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 1)
- 13-CA-5894; Columbia Broadcasting Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 155, Folder 2)
- 13-CA-5899; Hotel Sherman, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 3)
- 13-CA-5900; Avis Hotel, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 4)
- 13-CA-5902; Aetna Ball Roller Bearing Company, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 5)
- 13-CA-5903; Mojonnier Bros. Co., 1963 (Box 155, Folder 6)
- 13-CA-5906; King Car Wash, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 7)
- 13-CA-5912; Ohmite Manufacturing Company, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 8)
- 13-CA-5913; U. S. Steel Company, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 9)
- 13-CA-5914; Cosmetics Distributing, Inc., 1963 (Box 155, Folder 10)
- 13-CA-5915; Englander Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 155, Folder 11)
- 13-CA-5919; Alloy Steels, Inc., 1963 (Box 155, Folder 12)
- 13-CA-5921; National Tea Company, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 13)
- 13-CA-5922; Bluebird Coach Lines, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 14)
  Lyons, Illinois
- 13-CA-5924; Huber and Huber Motor Express, Inc., 1963 (Box 155, Folder 15)
  Louisville, Kentucky
- 13-CA-5928; Homemakers, Industries, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 16)
- 13-CA-5932; McGraw Construction Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 155, Folder 17)
  Middletown, Ohio
- 13-CA-5933; John Wood Company, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 18)
- 13-CA-5934; Imperial Eastman Corporation, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 19)
- 13-CA-5935; Denton Sleeping Garment Mills, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 20)
- 13-CA-5937; Reliable Manufacturing Company, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 21)
- 13-CA-5937; Reliable Manufacturing Company, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 22)
- 13-CA-5938; Laminet Cover Co., 1963 (Box 155, Folder 23)
- 13-CA-5938; Laminet Cover Company, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 24)
- 13-CA-5940; McDowell Truck Line, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 25)
- 13-CA-5944; Scam Instrument Corporation, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 26)